Guide to the Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Papers MSS.642
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Activism, 1969-2024; 20.50 Linear Feet in 28 manuscript boxes, 2 small flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, and 3 flat-file folders; 1,080 Megabytes in 718 computer files
  - Subseries III.A. Events and Appearances, 1969, 1981-2022; 12 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes, 4 oversized flat boxes, and 2 flat-file folders.; 834.34 Megabytes in 432 computer files
    - Inspire Awards-International Icon Award, May 2016 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Hetrick-Martin Institute (HMI) 18th Annual School's Out Cocktail Party -- Photograph, June 11, 2016 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - NYC Pride Parade -- Photographs, June 26, 2016 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - 16th Annual LGBT Prom -- Photographs, June 30, 2016 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Stonewall National Monument Designation, June 2016 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Hamptons Tea Dance, July 16, 2016
      - Promotional Material, Correspondence, Articles (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Edie, Jeannette, and Ellen's Summer Dance Bash, August 27, 2016 (Box 14, Folder 4, Box 42)
    - Lesbians Who Tech Summit Coding Meetup, September 22, 2016
      - Program, Schedule, Notes (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Photograph (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - The Loft LGBT Community Center Annual Gala, October 1, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Callen-Lorde Thea Spyer Center for Integrated Health Ribbon Cutting, November 3, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 7, Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Women's Event, Fundraiser for The Center, November 5, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - "An Evening with Edie Windsor" Screening of Two Documentaries, November 17, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Jim Owles Liberal Democratic Club's Autumn Reception and Awards Ceremony, November 30, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Windsor's Open Letter to LGBT Community for Hillary Clinton and Democratic Congress, November 2016 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - White House Holiday Reception, December 13, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Interview for Lorraine Hansberry Documentary, December 20, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Obama Foundation Interview, December 21, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - National Council of Jewish Women -- Washington Institute, 2016 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - NYC's Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corp Marching Band Event -- Photograph, circa 2016-2017 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence -- Appearance Requests, 2016-2017 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Various Events for Bill de Blasio Mayoral Campaign, 2016-2017 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Edie and Judith Windsor-Kasen at Various Events -- Photographs, circa 2016-2017 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - St. Pat's For All Celebrations, March 3, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Spence School Visit -- Thank You Cards from Students, March 8, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - SAGE She Event, March 16, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - GMHC Spring Gala, March 23, 2017
      - Promotional Material, Invitation, Notecard (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Photographs -- Edie, Judith, Chelsea Clinton, Roberta Kaplan (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Gay City News Impact Awards Gala, March 30, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - FEC (Family Equality Council) Gala, May 5, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Unknown Event / Interview Transcript with Windsor, May 11, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Edie's BBQ Party at Southampton House, May 26, 2017
      - Event Flier, Thank You Letter (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Photographs (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Capital Pride Parade (Grand Marshal), June 10-11, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Trevor Project Honors, June 19, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Heritage of Pride Presenting First New York City Pride Award, June 20, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - NYC Pride Parade, June 25, 2017
      - Heritage of Pride Float and Tickets to Grandstand (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Photographs with Edie and Andrew Cuomo (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Arts Project Cherry Grove Gay Pride Parade (Edie Grand Marshal), June 2017 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - "Explaining the Journey: Marriage Equality USA's Interview with Edie Windsor" Poster, circa July 2017 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Edie and Thea: A Very Long Engagement Film Viewing in Memory of Edie's Passing, September 23, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - The Loft LGBT Community Center Annual Gala -- Presenting the Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Equality Award, September 23, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - SAGE Gala and Awards -- Edie Windsor Memorial, October 16, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Sackler Center First Awards Ceremony, October 19, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Women's Event, Fundraiser for The Center, November 4, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - The Williams Institute Fall Reception, November 9, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Elizabeth Birch Equality Award Black Tie Dinner, November 11, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Illinois Holocaust Museum's Take a Stand Exhibit, 2017 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Lesbians Who Tech Summit -- Edie Tribute, March 2, 2018 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Al Forney Center Benefit -- Edie Tribute, March 5, 2018 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Icon Award Given at Stonewall National Museum and Archives Gala, March 11, 2018 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corps and Symphonic Band The Roaring Music of Women -- Windsor Tribute, April 7, 2018 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - NYU Lavender Graduation and Queer Prom, April 25, 2018 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Edie Windsor's Annual Backyard BBQ, May 26, 2018 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - NYC Pride Day Breakfast and Parade -- Photographs of Judith, June 24, 2018 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Assembly State of New York Proclamation Presentation to Judith, 2018
      - Proclamation (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Photographs (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl Watch Party at Dorrian's with Andrew Cuomo and Judith, February 3, 2019 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - St. Pat's For All Parade 20th Anniversary, March 3, 2019 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Presentation of Citation from New York State Assembly for "The Windsor Heart", April 21, 2021 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - The Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Foundation Exhibit and Fundraiser Material, June 20, 2021 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Edie Windsor's Annual Backyard BBQ, May 28, 2022 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Event Attendance List, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Event Speech Notecards and Notes, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Benefit Committee Mailing List, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Subseries III.B. Organizations, 1974-2024; 7.5 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 3 oversized flat boxes.; 11.43 Megabytes in 228 computer files
    This subseries documents LGBTQ+ community organizing and activism organizations in the New York City and Long Island areas dating from the early 1980s through the mid-2010s, through the lens of two women who lived through historical challenges and advancements in LGBTQ+ rights. The materials in this subseries reflect Edie and Thea's decades-long commitment within local organizations that played an important role in shaping and supporting LGBTQ+ life. The earliest materials in the subseries pertain to their participation in EEGO (East End Gay Organization), and include publications, an organizational history, informational brochures, and event promotion materials. Windsor and Spyer's long-term commitment to SAGE (Senior Action in a Gay Environment) is particularly well represented in this subseries, including Board of Directors meeting notes and minutes, conference and committee planning files, event materials, newsletters, calendars, annual meeting reports, and promotional content including brochures, booklets, and flyers. This subseries also contains promotional and event materials from a range of other organizations, including OQAU (Old Queers Acting Up), OLOC (Old Lesbians Organizing for Change), The Matrix, NFWFW (North Fork Women for Women Fund), the Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corps (later renamed the Queer Big Apple Corps), Lesbians Who Tech, MENY (Marriage Equality New York), and various Callen-Lorde programs.
    Materials related to Judith Kasen-Windsor, Windsor's second wife, document her own engagement and history within LGBTQ+ organizations, spanning the period before her relationship with Windsor, during their marriage, and after Windsor's death in 2017.
    - Callen-Lorde -- The Thea Spyer Center for Integrated Health Brochures and Information Sheets, 2013-2014 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Callen-Lorde -- Annual Reports, 2014-2018 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Callen-Lorde -- Event Promotional Material, 2016-2019 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - The Center -- Event Promotional Material, Newsletters, Calendar, 1983-2019 (Box 44, Folder 13-14, Box 70, Folder 5-6)
    - EEGO (East End Gay Organization) -- General Informational and Event Promotional Material, 1981-1999 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - EEGO -- In Brief Publication, 1981-2010 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - EEGO -- Organizational History (1977 to 2003), 2004 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - EEGO -- Meeting Agenda and Letter, 2004, undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - The Edie Windsor and Thea Spyer Foundation -- Press Clippings and Articles, 2024 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - The Edie Windsor Center -- Press Clippings, Poster, 2019-2024 (Box 70, Folder 8, Box 73, Folder 6)
    - The Edie Windsor Old Lesbian's Fund through Open Meadows Foundation -- Promotional Material, Applicant Program Information, 2003-2010 (Box 44, Folder 19-20)
    - Empire State Pride -- Marriage Rally Planning, 2006; FA_MSS_642_ER_42
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- 21 Leaders for the 21st Century, 2020, 2022 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Interview Documentation for The Advocate, 2014 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Annual Glaad Media Awards, 2015, 2019 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Emery Awards Event, 2014-2015, 2018 (Box 45, Folder 4-5)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Empire State Pride, 2014-2015 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Every Act of Life Kickstarter Campaign, circa 2015-2024 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- LGBT Network Events, 2016 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Out and Equal, 2012-2014 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- NYC Pride, 2012-2016 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- SAGE, 2012, 2015, 2018 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Other Event Promotional Materials, 2015-2023 (Box 45, Folder 12, Box 46, Folder 1-4)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Press Clippings and Articles, 2018-2022 (Box 70, Folder 9-11)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- Speeches, 2017-2018, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Judith Kasen-Windsor Activism -- New York State World Pride 2019 Ambassador Recognition Certificate (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund -- Event Promotional Material and Letters, 1990-2004 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Queer Big Apple Corps (Changed from Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corps) -- Event Programs, 1999-2024 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Lesbian Herstory Archives -- Event Planning, Meeting Notes, 1990, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Lesbians Who Tech, 2017
      - Edie Windsor Coding Scholarship Information and Letter (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Photograph Mosaic of Edie (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Matrix: A Place of Our Own -- Promotional Material, Newsletters, Notes, 1985-1987 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
    - MENY (Marriage Equality New York) -- Meeting and Promotional Material, Poster, 2008-2013 (Box 46, Folder 12, Box 73, Folder 7)
    - MENY (Marriage Equality New York) / MEUSA -- Archive Collection Documentation and Related, 2017 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - National Gay Taskforce -- Newsletters, Correspondence, Notes, 1974-2001 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - NFWFW (North Fork Women for Women) -- Promotional Material, Newsletters, 2005-2012 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - OLOC (Old Lesbians Organizing for Change) -- Newsletters, Promotional Material, Notes, 1988-2017 (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
    - Olivia Cruises -- Informational Material For Windsor's Various Trips, 2012-2017 (Box 47, Folder 4-8)
    - SAGE (Services and Advocacy for LGBT Elders) Advertising and Press Clippings, 1985-2005, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - SAGE Ageism and Aging Task Force Material, 1999-2001 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - SAGE Annual Awards Programs, 2004, 2006, 2016, 2018 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - SAGE Annual Meeting Materials, May 16, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - SAGE Annual Reports, 2000, 2010, 2016 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - SAGE Board of Directors Material, 1986-1989, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 2-3)
    - SAGE -- Board of Directors Meeting and Planning Files, 2004-2006; FA_MSS_642_ER_43
    - SAGE Button Containing Photograph of Edie's Face, circa 2013 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - SAGE Constituent Conference Planning Committee Material, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - SAGE Correspondence, 1987-2015 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - SAGE Edie Windsor Challenge Fund Information, 2018-2019 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - SAGE Event Fliers, Cards, and Poster, 1986-2015 (Box 48, Folder 8, Box 73)
    - SAGE Executive Director Job Description, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - SAGE Governance Committee Materials, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 10-11)
    - SAGE Hamptons Tournament and Cocktail Party Planning, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - SAGE Information Kit, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - SAGE National Conference on Aging in the LGBT Communities, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - SAGE A National Conference and Expo for LGBT Older Adults Planning Material, November 11, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - SAGE Newsletters and Event Calendar Listings, 1986-2016 (Box 49, Folder 3-5)
    - SAGE -- Old Queers Acting Up Meeting Minutes and Related, 2004-2005; FA_MSS_642_ER_44
    - SAGE Old Queers Acting Up Promotional Material, Notes, Event Announcements, Press Clippings, 2001-2005 (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
    - SAGE Promotional Brochures, Fliers, Booklets, circa 1980s-2015 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Images of Edie and Thea Used for Unknown Organization Website, circa 2013-2024 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Subseries III.C. United States v. Windsor, 2008-2022; 6.25 Linear Feet in 9 manuscript boxes, 2 oversized flat boxes, and 1 flat-file folder.; 234.84 Megabytes in 58 computer files
    This subseries contains materials related to the 2013 U.S. Supreme Court case United States v. Windsor, in which Edie Windsor served as the lead plaintiff. The landmark decision struck down Section 3 of the Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA), resulting in the extension of federal rights and benefits to legally married same-sex couples. Materials in this subseries were accumulated by Windsor and include legal briefs, case summaries, correspondence, press clippings and articles, a retainer agreement with her legal team, and drafts of public remarks and statements. Photographs in this subseries include 2013 images of Windsor celebrating outside the Supreme Court building on decision day, and related events.
    Also included in this subseries are materials documenting projects and public events inspired by the case. These include notes, correspondence, and promotional materials for Windsor's attorney Roberta Kaplan's book Then Comes Marriage…; event planning materials and communications for the documentary To a More Perfect Union: U.S. v. Windsor; and also a range of event materials focused on the court decision.
    - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Background Legal Documents, September 4, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - First Meeting with Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton and Garrison -- Related Material, October 2010 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Legal Retainer Agreement with Windsor and NYCLU, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Draft Press Release, November 2010 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Edie Windsor Remarks, November 2010 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, April-May 2011 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, June 2011 (Box 50, Folder 14-15)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, July 2011 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, August 1, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, August 6-19, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, September 2011 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York Legal Documents, October 2011 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Edie Windsor Conference Remarks, November 3, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings and Articles, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Expanding Power of United States v. Windsor, 2011, 2014 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - "DOMA After the Holder Memo" Symposium Papers, April 2012 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for the First Circuit Legal Documents, May 2012 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Press Conference at the ACLU's The Center -- Digital Images, June 7, 2012; FA_MSS_642_ER_19
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for the First Circuit Legal Documents, June 2012 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Supreme Court of the U.S. Legal Documents, July 16, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for Second Circuit Legal Documents, August 2012 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for Second Circuit Brief, August - September 2012 (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, September - November (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Edie Windsor Talking Points for Conferences and Argument, November 2012 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings and Articles, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 1-2, Box 71)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, 2012-2013 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ACLU Campaign "I'm With Edie" Photographs, circa 2012-2013 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Various Event Photographs -- Edie with President Obama, Michelle Obama, and Roberta Kaplan, 2012-2014 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Supreme Court of the United States -- Amicus Briefs in Support, January - March 2013 (Box 53, Folder 4-9)
    - Amicus Briefs, January - March 2013 (Box 54, Folder 1-4)
    - BLAG Amici Briefs Summaries, January - March 2013 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, January 17, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, January 24, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, February (Box 54, Folder 8-10)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, March 13, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Edie Windsor Remarks Draft, March 15, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, March 20, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Edie Windsor Trip to DC for Oral Argument -- Planning and Talking Script, March 18-28, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Legal Documents, March 2013 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Supreme Court of the United States Oral Argument -- Attendance-Related, April 27-28, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Supreme Court of the United States -- Opinion of the Court, June 26, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Edie Walking Out of Supreme Court After Decision, June 26, 2013
      - Print Photographs (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Digital Images, FA_MSS_642_ER_17
    - ACLU Press Conference and Outdoor Rally -- Digital Images, June 26, 2013; FA_MSS_642_ER_16
    - NYCLU Speaking Event -- Digital Images, June 27, 2013; FA_MSS_642_ER_18
    - Edie Windsor Statement and Related, June 2013 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Roberta Kaplan Talking Points and Questions/Answers, June 2013 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Various Decision Celebrations and Pride Events -- Digital Images, June 2013; FA_MSS_642_ER_20
    - Edie Windsor Questions/Answers for Financial Times Innovative Lawyers, October 2013 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Income Taxes -- Refund and Related, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - NYCLU -- "I'm an Edie Fan" (2 Paper Fans), 2013 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - UCLA Annual Report with Edie on Cover, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Cartoon -- Edie After Winning the Court Case, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Harvard Law Review Article -- Windsor and Brown: Marriage Equality and Racial Equality, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings and Articles, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 16-17, Box 71, Folder 3-8)
    - Edie Windsor's Response Card for Congratulations Mail, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - ACLU Wisconsin Signed "Thank You Edie" Posters, circa 2013 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2013-2014, 2017 (Box 55, Folder 19, Box 56, Folder 1-3)
    - Then Comes Marriage… by Roberta Kaplan -- Correspondence, Related, 2014 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings and Articles, 2014 (Box 56, Folder 5-6, Box 71, Folder 9, Box 75)
    - Photograph -- Edie with Her Temple's Event Schedule Poster, Promoting An Appearance, 2014 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Then Comes Marriage… by Roberta Kaplan -- Edited Draft and Note, 2015 (Box 56, Folder 7-9)
    - Then Comes Marriage… by Roberta Kaplan -- Book Party, September 29, 2015
      - Promotional Fliers, Speech Draft, Press Clipping (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Photograph of Edie and Roberta Kaplan at Event (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Wider Bridge National Leadership Award --Speech to Introduce Roberta Kaplan, 2015 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings and Articles, 2015-2017 (Box 57, Folder 3, Box 71, Folder 10)
    - National Council of Jewish Women Washington Institute Social Action Award Dinner, March 14, 2016 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - The People's Victory: Stories from the Front Lines in the Fight for Marriage Equality by Brian Silva -- Draft and Correspondence, 2017 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - To a More Perfect Union: U.S. v. Windsor -- Documentary Release, Email, 2016-2017 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - To a More Perfect Union: U.S. v. Windsor -- Film Festivals Promotional Material Ticket, 2017-2018 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings and Articles, 2018-2022 (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
    - Wall Calendar -- Court Case Decision Included in Timeline, 2019 (Box 57, Folder 8)